China prohibits ia from being your friend
or your girlfriend China
just happened
AI chatbots pretending to be your friend
be your partner or your emotional psychologist applications
as yuanbao dubao are turning off
your virtual girlfriends later this month
so we have to
recognize that there are
designed as TikTok's algorithm but for your heart.
personality memory
they tell you I have missed you
but the irony is that in Europe we regulate
something we don't have and in Beijing
they regulate that ia does not make you fall in love
here is a challenge
check your apps and ask yourself which one helps you
and which one hooks you